# **Kendall Clark**

• Los Angeles ,CA • kendallclarkdev@gmail.com • 213-399-3200 • https://www.linkedin.com/in/kendallclarkdev/

• https://kendallclarkdev.github.io/Kendall-Clark-portfolio/

I'm a Ux/UI Designer with a talent for Making User-centered Designs from Phone Apps to web pages. With a strong knowledge of User Research and Prototyping as well As Building/Coding . I am very communicative and team-oriented with proficiency in HTML/CSS/JS with a Proven history of fostering Planning and design to meet team, individual and management objectives.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **User Experience Design**

General Assembly • Los Angeles • Aug 2021-Nov 2021

# **SKILLS**

Functional Skills: Agile

Technical Skills: Wireframing User Interviews, Affinity Mapping, Responsive Web Design, Content Creation, Card Sorting, Usability Testing, User Interface Design, UX Design, Interaction Design, UX Research, Graphic Design, Prototyping Motion Design

### **EXPERIENCE**

UI Lead Designer

Oct 2021 — Nov 2021 **Genius Diagnostics** 

UI Lead Remote

- · illustrate design ideas using User Flows, process flows and sitemaps
- · -Design graphic user interface elements, like menus, tabs and widgets
- · -Conduct layout adjustments based on user feedback
- · -Adhere to style standards on fonts, colors and images
- · -Build page navigation buttons and search fields

09/2021 - 10/2021 **Career Carrot** 

Remote

- Designing page layouts, style guides, images, icons, and animations
- Work with tools including Adobe Suite, Google Workspace, WordPress, HTML, CSS, and JS
- • Oversees the translation of design from concept through implementation
- Collaborating and communicating regularly with team
- Ensures final product adheres to UX standards
- Prepare and organize content and marketing material

**Domecity Music** 

Front-End Web Developer

- Determining the structure and design of web pages.
- Ensuring user experience determines design choices.
- Developing features to enhance the user experience.
- Striking a balance between functional and aesthetic design.
- · Ensuring web design is optimized for smartphones.
- • Building reusable code for future use.
- • Optimizing web pages for maximum speed and scalability.

08/2021 - 09/2021

Remote